{
    "subject": "resource/Fablehaven:_Rise_of_the_Evening_Star",
    "predicate": "ontology/author",
    "object": "resource/Brandon_Mull",
    "human_readable": "Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star was written by Brandon Mull.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9698604345321655,
            "question": "Who wrote Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9061474204063416,
            "question": "Is Brandon Mull the author of a book called Fablehaven?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6668129563331604,
            "question": "What is the title of the book written by Brandon Mull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6577725410461426,
            "question": "What might be some themes explored in Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5749537348747253,
            "question": "If someone enjoys fantasy stories, would they likely enjoy Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5470914840698242,
            "question": "What genre is Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star likely to belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45213615894317627,
            "question": "Can you name a book by Brandon Mull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29528605937957764,
            "question": "Where could one find more information about Brandon Mull and his books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2699737548828125,
            "question": "Are there other books in the Fablehaven series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019401025027036667,
            "question": "What makes a good fantasy novel in your opinion?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star was written by Brandon Mull.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8264_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other books in the Fablehaven series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8264_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could one find more information about Brandon Mull and his books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8264_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a book by Brandon Mull?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8264_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8264_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all four files mention that \"Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star\" is written by Brandon Mull."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star\" is written by Brandon Mull, thus supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}